(Sheldon:)May I say something?
(Leonard:)Not right
now, Sheldon.
(Sheldon:)But I think it would
be comforting.
(Leonard:)Buddy...
No, it's okay.
(Penny:)What?
(Sheldon:)When I lost my own father,
(Sheldon:)I didn't have any friends
to help me through it.
(Bernadette:)You do.
(choked up): I really thought
he was gonna say, "Let it go."
(Raj(on phone):)Okay, thanks, Bernadette.
(Raj(on phone):)Travel safe.
(Raj(on phone):)Okay, bye.
(sighs)
They booked a flight.
(Raj(on phone):)They're heading
to the airport now.
(Penny:)How's Howard holding up?
(Raj:)He's hanging in there.
(Leonard:)How are you doing, Stuart?
(Stuart:)Still can't believe she's gone.
(Stuart:)I mean, that woman took me in.
(Stuart:)If it wasn't for her,
I-I would have been homeless.
(Amy:)One of us would
have taken you in.